

Submitted to Amentum for ARPA-H STATS

NAME	JOB TITLE	PWS Tasks
Soraya Schwartz	PXD - Intermediate	7.1.7; 7.8.1-7.8.3
	Conference/Events Planner	

Job Responsibility	Qualifying Skills
Event Planning & Logistics Coordination: Manage logistics for office events, including technical conferences, off-site meetings, and executive sessions.	 Successfully executed over 20 national and international seminars, symposiums, and workshops at George Washington University Cancer Center. Planned large-scale university commencement ceremonies with over 5,000 attendees, including staging, audiovisual, and scheduling logistics. Managed weekly and monthly meetings for National Association of Home Builders, ensuring smooth scheduling and room setup.
Vendor & Contract Management: Coordinate with vendors for venues, catering, audiovisual services, and other event-related needs.	 Coordinated vendor contracts for catering, venues, and conference technology at George Washington University and University of Phoenix. Successfully managed 30-40 vendor relationships for meetings and conferences at the National Association of Home Builders. Developed a process for reconciling invoices and ensuring timely vendor payments, improving vendor relationships.
Stakeholder Communication & Execution Support: Facilitate communication with internal and external stakeholders to ensure successful event execution.	 Served as the liaison between event planning teams, faculty, executives, and sponsors at George Washington University and University of Phoenix. Managed event marketing, participant communications, and digital promotions, increasing attendance and engagement. Developed internal communication materials such as agendas, newsletters, and promotional materials for high-profile university events.

Education

Loyola University New Orleans B.A. in Mass Communication

August 2005 - April 2011

George Washington University Professional Certificate in Event Management July 2018 - August 2020

Experience

The National Association of Home Builders, Washington, D.C. Event Specialist

March 2024 - October 2024

· Provided administrative and procurement services to the events department for a variety of events throughout the year.



- · Served as the primary point of contact for internal departments who needed conference room and food & beverage support for their meetings or events.
- · Processed internal and external billings for meetings/events.
- · Managed scheduling for building conference rooms for weekly/monthly meetings.
- · Organized a reconciliation process for all invoices to ensure clients were paid timely and accurately.
- · Assisted with event marketing to update website and social media platforms with department updates
- · Selected Achievements
- · Developed a new process for the reconciliation of invoices
- · Managed working with 30-40 vendors successfully for different meeting & event needs.

George Washington University Cancer Center, Washington, D.C.

Sr. Administrative Associate

October 2016 -September 2023

George Washington University Institute for Neuroscience, Program Coordinator

- Supervised budgets, logistics, event development, and faculty support for nationally recognized Centers at GW School of Medicine and Health Sciences
- · Provided enhanced administrative support to Center leadership, serving as liaison with faculty, staff, visitors, officials, donors, and national / international committees.
- · Directed Center digital marketing, event promotion, and internal communications, developing partnerships with professional associations and affiliated universities.
- · Developed and executed event calendar, managing annual Symposium and monthly Seminars from concept through implementation. Overseeing scheduling, logistics, vendors, staging, and audio-visual needs.
- · Facilitated day-to-day activities for senior leadership, from schedule management to developing detailed meeting agendas and presentations, to budget management and reconciliation.
- · Selected Achievements
 - Successfully executed 20 Seminars, drawing national and international attendance along with high-profile speakers.
 - Streamlined financial processes for institute faculty, from budgeting and procurement to reconciliation / audits.
 - Guided senior leadership and faculty in the shift to virtual office / virtual meetings during COVID-19. Included training staff and executives on web conferencing technologies, providing hands-on support for setup and execution, mentoring other admins with similar challenges.

University of Phoenix, Washington, D.C. Academic Affairs Coordinator

May 2014 - October 2016

- Managed event planning and logistics, faculty support, and student engagement across four campuses in VA and DC
- · Planned and coordinated day-to-day events for faculty and students, including meetings, conferences, workshops.
- Managed annual Commencement activities, including scheduling, logistics, vendors, staging and audio-visual needs.
- · Oversaw monthly budgets and payroll, managed faculty scheduling, evaluations, performance reports.
- · Wrote and edited campus newsletters, faculty / student communications, and regional marketing materials.
- · Selected Achievements
 - Organized large-scale Commencements drawing over 5,000 students, faculty, and family members.
 - Successfully executed multiple seminars and quarterly faculty meetings for groups in excess of 150 people.
 - Managed two successful accreditation reviews for the regional campus, maintaining critical department and faculty files.
 - Measurably improved process flows, service quality, and customer satisfaction scores related to Academic Affairs.



Latin American Youth Center, Washington, D.C. Case Manager, Teen Bridge Program

June 2013 - Feb. 2014

- · Supported foster care youth (ages 16-21) in developing self-sufficiency in education, employment, and life skills.
- · Conducted initial intakes, developed case plans, assessments, and monthly client reports, led discharge planning.
- · Collaborated with outside providers to ensure client progress, access to employment-related services, and aftercare.
- · Taught life management skills, helping youth problem-solve daily issues to promote independence.
- · Attended family court hearings to present program views on client progress and needs.

Medtech College, Washington, D.C. Student Services Coordinator

Nov 2011 - Jan 2013

- · Implemented support services to help challenged students in achieving their academic goals.
- · Planned and executed events such as: student orientation, graduation, enrichment speakers, and fundraisers.
- · Developed the Medtech Career Fair, working with the Career Center to identify internship opportunities.
- · Connected students with agencies in the Washington D.C. area for childcare, housing, and medical needs.
- · Advised and supported prospective students through the application and class registration process.

Additional Qualifications & Experience

- · Fluent in Spanish (written and spoken)
- · Advanced Microsoft Office skills; proficient with Oracle
- · Advanced skills with web conferencing systems
- · Event planning for weddings, working with local event company to assist in location scouting, vendor management, event setup and execution, digital marketing
- · Familiar with Adobe InDesign